<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Orcs Attack!</string>
    <string name="app_description">Orcs Attack! is a collection of small programs that help you DM your pen and paper RPG.</string>


    <string name="test">This is my test string</string>

    <string name="add_to_party">Add to party</string>

    <string name="about_app">This app is a work in progress. It is being developed by myself in my spare time as a hobby and a way to learn more about Android developement. This app is completely ad-free and collects absolutely no personal data. If you want to report a bug
    or have an idea for a feature for the app, please contact me! I will be very glad to hear you out and try my best to implement it. Seriously, I would love hearing from you!
        All the code is open-source and available on <a href="https://www.github.com/arkountos/Initiative-Tracker">Github</a>. Feel free to check it out!
    </string>

    <string name="about_rate">If you enjoyed this app, give it a good rating! If not, give it a bad one! Eitherway, I would very much appreciate you contacting me with your thoughts and views on the app and thoughts on making it better.</string>

    <string name="about_attributions">The character and tile art for this application is from flaticon! Check them out here
        <div><a href="https://www.flaticon.com/authors/freepik" title="Freepik">Freepik</a> from <a href="https://www.flaticon.com/" title="Flaticon">www.flaticon.com</a>,<br /></div> <div><a href="https://www.flaticon.com/authors/smashicons" title="Smashicons">Smashicons</a> from <a href="https://www.flaticon.com/" title="Flaticon">www.flaticon.com</a></div>
        Content provided in this app is Open Gaming Content, published in the Systems Reference Document (SRD) available at dnd.wizards.com, licenced under Open Gaming Licence, Vesion 1.0a.
    </string>

    <string name="battle_to_start">Dynamic Battle Tracker</string>

    <string name="campfire_help">When you check the campfire box, a campfire appears near the middle of your map. If a campfire is present, allied characters appear close to the fire while enemy characters appear far from it.
    If no campfire is present, all the characters appear randomly. You can set the max distance from the fire that ally characters can spawn, as well as the minimum distance from the campfire for enemies to spawn from the settings tab.</string>

    <string name="artwork_jason">The background images were created by Jason Milios!</string>

    <string-array name="classes">
        <item>Barbarian</item>
        <item>Bard</item>
        <item>Cleric</item>
        <item>Druid</item>
        <item>Fighter</item>
        <item>Monk</item>
        <item>Paladin</item>
        <item>Ranger</item>
        <item>Rogue</item>
        <item>Sorcerer</item>
        <item>Warlock</item>
        <item>Wizard</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="NPC_charisma_checks">
        <item>Deception</item>
        <item>Intimidation</item>
        <item>Flirting</item>
        <item>Bribery</item>
        <item>Persuasion</item>
        <item>Blackmailing</item>
        <item>Bartering</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="NPC_secrets">
        <item>Has committed murder</item>
        <item>Holds a recently stolen item</item>
        <item>Bounty-hunters are after him/her</item>
        <item>Has wronged an old friend</item>
        <item>Knows the true identity of an important political figure</item>
        <item>Holds a kidnapped person</item>
        <item>Has connection to a thieves guild</item>
        <item>Holds a long lost book about wizardry</item>
        <item>Knows the lair of a Dragon</item>
        <item>Has power over a ruling politician</item>
        <item>Is a very wealthy/powerful person in disguise</item>
        <item>Knows the position of a magic artifact</item>
        <item>Knows how to get to the lair of a bandit group</item>
        <item>Knows how to get to the lair of a powerful dark wizard</item>
        <item>Knows the secret code to get to an exclusive club/base</item>
        <item>Is planning on robbing/killing someone very soon</item>
        <item>Is a spy for a foreign power</item>
        <item>Is a doppelganger in disguide</item>
        <item>Know the road to an unknown place of power</item>
        <item>Knows a secret about an important figure in a nearby village/town</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="NPC_characteristics">
        <item>Has a glass eye</item>
        <item>Walks with an oddly long cane</item>
        <item>Cannot talk because of a spell</item>
        <item>Speaks very slow</item>
        <item>Speaks very fast</item>
        <item>Does not speak common</item>
        <item>Has a scar on his/her face</item>
        <item>Has a wooden leg</item>
        <item>Has very long hair</item>
        <item>Has an ear cut off</item>
        <item>Is very beautiful</item>
        <item>Is really ugly</item>
        <item>Bites his/her nails</item>
        <item>Has very long fingers</item>
        <item>Is almost naked</item>
        <item>Refers to him/herself with his/her name</item>
        <item>Smokes a pipe</item>
        <item>Wears very big glasses</item>
        <item>Has bright blue hair</item>
        <item>Wears oversized clothes</item>
        <item>Smells wonderful</item>
        <item>Smells bad</item>
        <item>Has a dog follower</item>
        <item>Has a cat follower</item>
        <item>Animals always stay near him/her</item>
        <item>Has a very soft and calm voice</item>
        <item>Only talks with a few words</item>
        <item>Is always angry/irritated</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="NPC_useful_info">
        <item>Was friends with the last king of the land</item>
        <item>Used to live in a now gone city and knows it's history</item>
        <item>Can point to a secret magic shop</item>
        <item>Can point to a druid's shop in the woods</item>
        <item>Can give the characters info on the surrounding woods</item>
        <item>Can give the characters info on the political situation in a nearby town</item>
        <item>Knows about the type of monsters that lurk around the area he/she lives</item>
        <item>Knows another adventuring party and their location</item>
        <item>Knows people that have quests for the party</item>
        <item>Knows lore about a historical event of the land</item>
        <item>Knows a famous song</item>
        <item>Knows a famous fairytale of the land</item>
        <item>Knows about an old prophecy</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="positive_button">OK</string>
    <string name="negative_button">Cancel</string>

    <string name="dialog_string">This is a test dialog for hitpoints</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
